I'm quite far from the city.
This should suffice.
After all. nobody knows what might happen.
Job-change quest.
This quest appeared
when I reached level 40.
There have been two dungeons
that are opened with keys.
Aside from penalties and urgent quests.
this is the first time
the system directly intervenes.
And this quest
is different from the others.
I can choose whether to accept
and when to start.
Does it suggest it's that challenging?
Generally speaking.
this quest should reward me
with professional skills.
I can become stronger.
Yes.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Damn. I haven't completed
the daily quest yet.
Fine. I'll do it when I get back.
All right.
I finally feel like the game has started.
I wonder what awaits me inside.
How exciting.
Sorry. I'm late.
No. you are right on time. Jinsung.
Long time no see. Jinho.
Brother.
This dungeon is more ordinary
than I imagined.
I can't use potions
and Full Recovery here?
I can't leave until I complete it.
I have to be cautious.
An armor-type monster?
My attack has no effect?
It's useless?
Enemies with a hard shell...
I've faced them before!
I wasted a Fatal Strike.
Here. neither my injury
nor my mana will recover.
However...
Of course you guys don't care. do you?
What's the matter. Jinho?
You're not eating.
Ah. nothing.
Jinsung.
How's the progress with the guild?
I've heard that S-rank hunters
have refused to join.
Indeed. Min Byung-gu and Cha Hae-In
both declined our invitation.
But it doesn't affect our plan.
We are negotiating with hunters
from Europe and the Middle East.
They will join us
if we offer enough money.
After all. there's the precedent
set by Hunter Hwang Dongsoo.
That's true.
Abroad... I see.
Jinho.
I know you are up to something.
You've been bidding high prices
for numerous C-rank raid missions
to try to make your achievements.
It doesn't matter if it's for fun.
but remember...
don't get in my way.
Brother doesn't know how strong Jinwoo is.
With Jinwoo's strength.
I can...
I'm getting tired from fighting non-stop.
Now I can take a break...
Stealth?
They even know how to use Stealth?
Next is a mage.
And he's using flash magic.
Stealth and flash magic.
What's with this place?
That hard shell like Kasaka's...
It's like a review of my past battles.
This quest is harder than I thought.
I must use different abilities to deal
with different types of monsters.
I should use strength for knights.
perception for assassins.
and agility for archers.
Without strength. I can't damage knights.
If my perception is too low.
I can't detect assassins.
But the bigger problem
is the mage.
They should be dealt with intelligence.
Sadly. I haven't invested much
in intelligence.
As a result. my mana is insufficient.
Although I want to conserve my skills...
my fatigue is accumulating.
I need to finish this quickly.
So. is everyone here?
Finally.
Even a thing like this is valuable.
Fortunately. I could get some
from monsters.
High-rank knight's chestplate?
Right. I've never tried on the equipment.
They can turn invisible?
Great. The equipment
doesn't change my appearance.
Nor do they hinder my movements.
It's hard to feel that
since I can't use Full Recovery now.
but I've leveled up.
I obtained some items and gold coins
and my fatigue has also recovered.
It should be about time I move on.
Okay.
How strong will my opponent
behind this door be?
Since I can't leave without defeating him.
I have to go forward.
This terrifying aura.
Is this the king's hall?
My eyes. ears. fingertips...
and my whole body remember this.
the same aura I felt
in the double dungeon.
The source of this astonishing aura
is him?
"Knight Commander. Igris the Bloodred."
His name is in crimson.
He's obviously on a different level
from the other beasts.
A knight who defends the empty throne.
He's coming.
He chops pillars
as easily as snapping a twig.
Being strong is an understatement.
He wears such cumbersome armor.
yet he moves so fast.
He's incredibly strong.
I can't cut through.
I can reach his speed.
but he's extremely destructive.
My dagger can't penetrate his armor.
Can I really defeat him?
A strong enemy beyond my imagination.
However...
I don't think I can defeat you unarmed.
but this is the only way
to cause internal damage
through the armor.
Is this what they call chivalry?
You underestimate me?
Come in.
President. are you not going home yet?
I don't want to go back yet.
So I stayed to handle some other work.
Same for me.
I've completed extra work too.
It's finally starting.
Speaking of the devil.
It's me. Are you setting off now?
Yes.
I want to thank you first
for agreeing to this operation.
You don't need to thank me.
This is the result of you repeatedly
mentioning the Jeju Island incident
on TV interviews and magazine features.
That's how the public
remembered the tragedy.
and their attitude was changed.
I am simply adding
a bit of momentum to the tide.
Won't they criticize you
for looking for trouble?
I'm well-prepared for that.
But you must be careful.
Jeju Island is a dangerous area.
I know that very well.
Our mission this time is reconnaissance.
We'll launch a minor attack
to probe the enemy's strength and size.
I admire your effort.
The third Jeju Island raid mission.
for me.
is still not over.
He's fast.
I was on the defensive.
but I think I still lost
500 points of vitality.
It was the right decision to wear armor.
If he had hit me directly.
I could have been killed on the spot.
He has such strength even without a sword.
He's too strong.
If I can't match his strength.
I'll increase my speed.
I can't catch up.
The passive skill
has increased my defense.
That should do it.
I...
I haven't
lost yet!
That dagger cannot be transferred.
It will go back into the inventory.
and come back to me!
I stabbed too shallow.
I need to stab deeper.
I won... right?
That was really close.
I was lucky to defeat him.
In terms of skill. strength.
and experience.
I am not his match in any aspect.
If I had made a mistake.
I would have died.
Four rewards?
A pouch carrying 1.500.000 gold coins.
The same helmet as Igris'.
It's an S-rank item!
The Demon Castle's Key is also S-rank.
but this is my first S-rank gear.
It reduces physical damage by 15%
and increases vitality and strength
by another 20 points.
That's awesome.
And the stone Ruler's Hand.
What kind of skill is this?
Never mind. I'll find out later.
Aside from those...
Instant teleportation stone?
It can't go back into the inventory.
Why does it appear now?
Is it because
this job-change quest
is still not over?
The longer I hold out. the more points?
What's a high-class job?
"Good luck"?
An infinite number of enemies?
If they are of Igris' level.
I might not last even a few seconds.
But my current ability is
more than enough for these ones.
But. there are too many.
Damn it.
No matter how many I kill.
they keep coming out of the gate.
The key to this quest
is how long I can hold out.
In that case...
Activating Stealth takes 200 mana.
Afterwards. it costs one mana per second.
I have 190 mana left.
I must buy as much time as possible.
My Stealth has been detected?
I didn't expect that.
Both Stealth and Murderous Intent
are now useless.
How long has it been?
Only five minutes?
I have no chance.
I'll have to use the teleportation stone.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm